Bradley, Phillips, Papers /3043
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Phillips Bradley Papers
1941-1950
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bradley, Phillips
/3043
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Correspondence and pamphlets collected by Mr. Bradley for the Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions of the New York State Legislature in connection with the founding of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University.
3074717
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5693: Labor Editorial Files
Bradley, Phillips,1894-1982.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3074717
- Workmen's Compensation Board, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Workmen's Compensation Board - Annual Report 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Compensation Insurance Rating Board, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Memo to Ives Day Great, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Day, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR - Report and act Estab. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Trip - Schedule - Hotels, Etc., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bradley's Schedule (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bradley's Wares, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Complete Itinerary, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Fisher, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Interviews (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bradley - Queens, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Report, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ann Arbor, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Chicago, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Denver, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Detroit, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fargo, North Dakota, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Kansas City, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Los Angeles, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Madison, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Milwaukee, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Minneapolis, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Portland, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- San Francisco, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Seattle, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- St. Louis, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Thank You Letters, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Industrial Relations, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Industrial and Labor Relations, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Copies of the Amer. Story of ILR (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Conference on Contemporary Problems in Labor Law and Relations, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- New York State School of industrial and Labor Relations Cornell Industry, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Alabama, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Connecticut, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Alaska, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Arizona, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Arkansas, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- California, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Colorado, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Delaware, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- District of Columbia, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Florida, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Georgia, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Idaho, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Illinois, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Indiana, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Iowa, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Kansas, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Kentucky, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Louisiana, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Maine, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Maryland, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Michigan, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Minnesota, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Mississippi, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Missouri, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Montana, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Nebraska, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Nevada, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- New Hampshire, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- New Jersey, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- New Mexico, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- New York, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- North Carolina, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- North Dakota, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Ohio, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Oklahoma, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Oregon, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Pennsylvania, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Rhode Island, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- South Carolina, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- South Dakota, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Tennessee, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Texas, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Utah, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Vermont, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Virginia, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Washington, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- West Virginia, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Wisconsin, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Wyoming, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Report to the Board of Temporary Trustees NYSSILR, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Report of the Industrial Commissioner to the Restaurant Minimum Wage Board, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Report of the Industrial Commissioner to the Restaurant Minimum Wage Board, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  Board
- New York State Economy Commission Preliminary Report No. 5, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Unit Comments, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Clippings: Miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Review Copies Education Professional Trade Journals, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Com - Unit - Various Docs., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Unit - General Correspondence, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Com - Unit - Classroom Activities - Films, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Com - Unit - Outline Tic., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Unit - Reviews + Comments "Amer. Story", 1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Com - Unit Data, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Source Material: Allied Traders Unit, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Material Not Used :Unit, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Corrections on Unit, 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Picture Sources: Unit, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Cal Inst. Of Tech., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Univ. California. E.S.M.W.T., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- News and Views Chicago Public Schools, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- University of Colorado, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- University of Denver, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Denver Opportunity School (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Fargo North Dakota, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Occidental College Los Angeles, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- University of Michigan Extension, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Minnesota Labor Relations Act., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- University-Minnesota Workers Educational, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Rockhurst. College (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Wisconsin Rural Adult Education, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cal. State Dept. of Educ. Industrial Relations Training, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Denver Adult Edu. -Council-, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Calif. State Dept. Ed. Ind. Rel., 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- California Labor School, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- City of Los Angeles, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- California Reemployment and Reconstruction, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- N.Y. Miscellaneous, 1940-1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Administrative Adjudication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Mediation and Arbitration, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Disability and Insurance, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Labor Relations, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Lyon, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Regional Planning, 1943-1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- State + Federal Disability Insurance Plans, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Teamsters Union Pacific Coast, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Wage Plans of Dep All, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Guaranteed Wages, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Women - Miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Workers Education, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Workers Education, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)